Subtitles by explosiveskull
One, two, three, four.
♪ When I look into your eyes ♪
♪ What do I hope to see? ♪
♪ You're just a reflection ♪
♪ Just make believe ♪
♪ You're just a projection ♪
♪ 'Cause inside
You're dead like me ♪
♪ 'Cause you're not free ♪
♪ You beg and plead ♪
♪ Get down on your knees ♪
♪ You and me will never be ♪
♪ 'Cause baby
You're dead like me ♪
♪ Oh, you're dead like me ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, no ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ You're dead to me ♪
Once there was a band,
three people brought
together by music.
I brought my axe,
Rachel brought her golden voice,
and Scott brought the tunes.
And there was sex, and drugs,
and murder, and mayhem,
and a bunch of other shit
you won't believe.
I wouldn't.
It all started
one dark and stormy night.
I was celebrating my 50th
birthday for the third time.
Who the hell are you people?
And what the hell
are you listening to?
I let my daughter
Chloe sponsor the party
with some vodka company,
just to make a few bucks.
She was a hustler,
a real ball-buster
like her old man.
So of course,
she put on the one song I hate.
You heard this one, haven't you?
Every few years it ends up
in a beer commercial,
number one on the charts,
my one hit, my meal ticket.
I peaked at 20,
and I've been circling
the bowl of this
business ever since.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be happy
if I never had to hear
that fucking song again.
Oh, but it's your birthday,
Pops.
Sorry, sorry.
Are you sure this
is the right house?
Dude, I don't know.
All these houses
in the hills look the same,
so let's just assume it is.
- Pardon me.
- Oh!
Dude!
- What's up?
- This fucking house is sick.
Look at that shit.
Are you shootin'?
Wanna leave your
guitar in the car, man?
Fuck, you know what?
You start playing
Kumbaya for the chicks.
Go fuck yourself, okay?
Stop.
Party over here!
Thank you, sweetie.
Did fate bring them to me
or was it random?
- Who knows?
- What's that?
Turn, turn, turn.
Fuckin' Dirt Pipe,
- remember them?
- Holy shit!
- Yeah, by Jimmy Kleen.
- Jimmy Kleen, yeah, yeah.
He had that hit in the '80s?
- Come on.
- I tell you this much,
opportunity walked
right up to me,
and I almost punched
his lights out.
Story of my life.
Check out those guitars,
dude, that's sick.
Hey, no cameras!
Who the fuck are you guys?
You brought your own guitar?
Come here.
Come over here.
You here to play me your demo?
No.
Then why the fuck are you
at my house, at my party?
I followed a girl here.
That's how I got here, too.
Here, come on, take a seat.
You like that, huh?
The Rickenbacker 12-string.
It's the hollow body.
Harrison had one.
Man knows his scripture.
Can I play it?
Can I fuck your sister?
Play yours.
Come on, destiny awaits.
Who is that?
I was going to ask you.
I have no idea.
Friend of yours?
That's the girl.
You're not going over there,
are you?
It's beautiful.
Hey, where are you going?
I... I can't.
Come on, you just did.
I'm Jimmy.
What's your name?
I'm Rachel.
Hey, come here.
This is...
I'm Scott.
You sounded great.
You, too.
Thanks.
Let her have a seat,
- caveman.
- Sorry, sorry.
Hey,
let me ask you something.
You guys ever been in a band?
I had to get us playing fast,
to see if she had the goods.
I could tell she was skittish,
but she liked Scott,
so I figured I could
control her through him.
Male, female, yeah?
Excuse me.
Come over here.
Stand here.
No, I don't... I don't wanna be
the center of attention,
I just...
want to be in the band.
You're over here.
So what's a band?
It's a statement, an ethos,
where everything
means something.
Nirvana just didn't happen
to dress like roadies.
That was a decision.
The Beatles bowed after
every song, that was a choice.
You know, it's all calculated.
It's all created.
It's all about the concept.
And our concept
centers around you.
You're in charge,
you're the front man.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm the band leader.
The front man
stands in the front,
you engage the audience.
I'm the band leader.
I'm with the band,
keep the train on schedule.
Our concept was
never just her.
- Yeah.
- It's us.
We are a band, we are one.
But it's not Hollow Bodies,
it's Hollow Body.
Trust me.
You're the star.
We want every girl
to want to be her
and all the guys
want to fuck her.
We want every girl
to want to fuck you.
All right, fine.
Well, band leader....
- Yeah.
- What do you want to start with?
Let's start with "Perfect Day,"
seems fitting.
All right.
One, two...
That's my part.
One, two, three, four.
Scott was easy to figure out.
I was him, once.
Trying to balance
the work with the wife.
Something's gotta give.
What's her name, this girl?
Rachel.
How old is she?
I don't know.
What, you were there all night
and you don't know
how old she is?
What am I, on trial now, Carrie?
I mean...
Okay, um...
It's just... It's just strange.
You trust me.
I trust you.
I would never...
never do anything
to mess this up.
♪ What can I say? ♪
See?
♪ I love you in every way ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
It's good.
Thanks.
And then there was
Rachel and Barb.
I hadn't counted on Barb.
Stage mom.
Barb's been pimping Rachel out
for a long time now.
She's a grown-up version of
the kind of groupie you'd see.
Do anything or anyone
to get on the bus.
Shouldn't you not be
drinking with your medicine?
Don't you worry about me.
I'm going to outlive all of you.
How old did he say he was?
Who?
That Scott.
I don't know.
Well, is he 40?
He's 33.
Isn't that old to be still
doing this, don't you think?
Jimmy's 50-something.
Well, he's a name.
He has connections.
What has Scott got?
Talent.
What do you know about him?
He's married.
He's got a baby.
A husband and a father.
How's he supporting his
family while he's doing this?
Why do you care?
Sweetheart, I'm just
making sure you're protected.
It's special.
These entertainment people,
you know what they can be like.
I had my own problems.
I'm underwater
in this stupid house
and I have to go beg
from Richie Rolands.
Richie runs
a multinational media empire
that he inherited from his dad,
who I once made
a ton of cash for.
Now I got to go kiss
Junior's ring.
So who's fucking her?
You?
This guy?
Is she a tomcat in the sack?
What's the deal? Talk to me.
A tomcat's a male cat.
Just listen to the track.
Just send me the link.
You want me to listen to it
on your bullshit phone speakers?
Come on, man.
- Well, come up to the studio.
- I got to go in a minute.
Listen, I'm not her dad.
If she wants to fuck you,
she can fuck you.
That's why you're not
fucking her, right?
Because you're like
her dad or something?
Hell, man, you look like shit.
How are you living like this?
I mean, what's going on?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm getting fat
and my house is falling apart.
Everything just went to shit
after this bitch left me.
How did Chloe take it?
Oh, that's not Chloe's mom,
that was the one before.
You know,
but Chloe threw a party,
she burned her furs in effigy.
Chip off the old block, huh?
Well, I'll give you this,
she's got a look.
- She's got it all.
- So what?
I mean, how many YouTube subs
does she have?
What kind of metrics
are we talking about?
Come on, man, that's the way
things are going these days,
- you got to keep up.
- Now, don't give me that.
She is gold and I can spot gold.
Come on, Richie.
You know...
the last time you called me
Richie, I was an unpaid intern
and you were too fucking high
to remember my name.
So try and remember now,
now it's Rick.
Sorry, Rick.
You're just not that memorable.
She is.
Well, see, the thing is,
and you don't seem
to be getting this,
is I don't really do
A & R anymore, okay?
I'm launching a music
streaming platform,
I'm not trying to
sign your little band.
And just a bit of advice:
you should move on.
You're fucking 50, all right?
Have you looked
in a mirror lately?
You can't be out there
shaking your ass.
That's why I need this to work.
Why'd you even
come over anyway, then?
I came over here out of
respect to our friendship,
because we go way back.
And my physical therapist
is right around the corner,
he's actually Geffen's guy.
All right, look.
I know a guy,
he's always looking
for opening acts.
Maybe I can get you
a West Coast tour
or something,
how does that sound?
- Yeah, we can do that.
- No frills.
I don't care about
accommodations.
All I care about are advances.
Fifty grand or something.
Oh, an advance?
You want an advance?
What is this, 1989?
Get 500,000 Instagram followers
and then talk to me
about an advance.
Ten grand, anything?
I love you, man.
I really do,
I get a kick out of ya.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna
text you the guy's info.
And I'm going to send
my maids over.
Thanks, Richie.
Rick.
It's time to start playing out.
You hear me?
- Already?
- Yeah.
Don't you think it's too soon?
I mean, yeah,
are you sure we're ready?
It's the only way
to spread the word.
to really get good.
All right.
Yeah, when we play out,
there's no safety net.
We don't have guitar techs,
so you have to tune,
change your strings,
hook up the PA, you got to
be good, you got to be fast.
All right?
And you have to
command the stage.
They're there to see
a performance.
Something they'll remember.
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
♪ You make the world
worth fighting for ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
♪ You make the world
worth fighting for ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
All right, let's do it again.
- Uh, can I help you?
- Oh, uh, the door was open.
- I'm here for Rachel.
- Oh, you must be her mom.
Barb.
I'm Jimmy.
Well, you're in
pretty good shape
for an older guy.
Older than what?
I'm probably the oldest woman
that's ever been in this house.
I wouldn't say that exactly.
You raised
quite a talented daughter.
Yes, I did.
You look kind of
beat up in this one.
That was a long time ago.
And yet, there it is
on the wall like you miss it.
More of a cautionary tale.
We all carry the seeds of
our own destruction, Mr. Klein.
You're telling me.
Mom?
What are you doing here?
Oh, honey,
I thought we could have lunch.
Hi, I'm Scott.
You're the writer.
I can see why she likes you.
Well, I mean,
actually we kind of
all write the songs.
Some of them are quite good.
Thanks.
But where is this all going?
Well, I wasn't
going to mention this
but since you're here,
there is label interest
and a few touring dates.
A tour?
Just West Coast dates.
So, is this part
of a record deal?
No, there's nothing concrete,
there's no advance.
It's just for some exposure.
- Twelve dates, fourteen days.
- Hm.
Look, I'm just not
sure about all this.
Come on, haven't you ever
road-tripped before?
Every summer.
Perfect.
We have to talk about this,
Rachel.
Let's go,
say goodbye to your friends.
Ah, Barb,
playing hard to get.
We hit the road
two weeks after that,
one last run.
Getting out there again,
I got excited.
I thought maybe
my luck had changed.
It did.
It got worse.
How are you doing?
All right, listen,
this is the perfect crowd.
They're just drunk enough.
Good training wheels.
Just seems
like a lot of people.
I once played to 40,000
people on three hits of acid.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, that's what they told me.
I don't remember shit
but if I can do that,
you can do this.
Look at that guy,
do you even care what he thinks?
It's just like rehearsal,
all right?
Okay.
Do you trust me?
No.
Well, good.
That's 'cause you're smart.
Look, here, it's going to get
hot under the lights.
You're going to have
to take this off.
Jimmy.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
You look beautiful.
Thanks.
See, I told you.
Okay.
You're on.
All right, let's go, guys.
Hey, we're Hollow Body.
And we're from Los Angeles.
"Perfect Day."
One, two, three, four.
Are you okay?
Do you guys think
I like the road?
Carrying my own gear?
Bad food and truck stop shits?
No, but that's the road.
You do your fucking job
and you get on with it.
Dude, she had a bad night.
Yeah, well you better get
your shit together, honey,
'cause Mommy's not here
to fucking help you anymore.
She gets it,
just give her time.
Oh, time?
Let me tell you about time.
You're 33 years old
with a wife and a kid.
She's 23 years old.
She's got five or six more
fuck-ups in her life.
You have no Plan B.
And this is Plan A.
Fucking bullshit.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
- No, hey, hey,
don't listen to that
fucking dickhead.
Bullshit.
Put that fucking camera down
or I'll stick it up
your fucking ass.
Think he's fucking Scorsese.
Goddamn it!
Shit!
What the hell's the problem now?
It's the battery.
Neil said it was touchy.
It's not fucking working.
Nice.
This was a fucking
embarrassment in there.
I had to pull
favors for that gig.
- It makes me look bad.
- Next time, she'll be ready.
Next time?
There isn't gonna be
a next time.
If she can't tour,
it's fucking done.
I'll sing lead
for a couple of shows.
It's not a big deal!
You think the frat boys
came out to see you?
Listen,
you're just along for the ride.
You're a decent songwriter,
an okay singer,
and quite frankly,
- a shitty guitarist.
- You know what?
- You know what I'm good at?
- What?
Getting her
to put up with your bullshit.
You're just a fucking has-been
who hasn't written
a goddamn good song
in 20 fucking years.
Well, bite me!
Finally we get
some focus back!
Fuck you,
you fucking piece of shit!
Fuck you.
I like seeing you
get mad, finally.
Fuck off, Zach!
Your mommy's here.
Okay, this?
All this...
is over.
This is all too much for her.
So sweetheart,
let's just go home.
Get in the car.
Now.
Rachel.
Are you all right?
Jesus fuck!
Rachel, Rachel, Rachel!
I understand second chances.
I've almost died a few times.
Overdose here, overdose there,
stabbed in prison even.
There's no white light.
But Rachel's not like me.
She's fragile.
This could have broke her.
Or maybe Barb dying
would finally set Rachel free.
Man, was I wrong about that.
So you think after that
she'd take it easy.
Wrong.
She went crazy.
And of course Chloe was there
to enable all her bad behavior.
- Here.
- I get it.
Cheat death,
you don't cash out,
you double down.
Wow.
You never did that before.
There's a lot of things
I've never done before, huh?
Yes,
another proof of concept, yes.
I'm going to try every
single one of them.
Good, you ready to go on?
No, that part still scares me.
You've got this.
You just need to, like,
loosen up a little bit,
and don't get too drunk.
I kind of like getting drunk.
Do you wanna...
try something?
Like what?
Like him?
You want me to...
Yes.
Go, kiss a stranger.
Just make out with somebody.
Work off some of this...
nervous energy.
I've got to go.
Hey, don't take too long.
You're on soon.
- Yeah.
- If you don't, I will.
Oh, my God.
Hi.
Sorry, um...
Oh.
Hey, you okay?
You okay?
You all right?
Dude, this thing is amazing.
Yeah, just don't mess it up.
Stacey's not allowed
at this event.
I'll be gentle.
I don't like her,
make her leave.
Thanks for setting this up,
baby.
Oh, please,
I'm doing this for Rachel.
Not you, old man.
This is what you have
to look forward to
when you get older.
No, he looks like
he's probably a good dad.
As long as he doesn't
keep hanging out with you.
That's my girl.
Rachel, we're on.
Coming.
Ladies and gentlemen,
next up, we have...
Hollow Body.
Hey, we're Hollow Body.
Don't kill animals...
unless they have
it coming to them.
Porky!
And the star of our show,
Ms. Rachel Swann!
What's this?
Thought we could
try something new.
Okay.
All right, fellas.
How's everybody feeling
out there?
All right, she wants to try
something new here.
Something new?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Yeah, don't worry,
it's easy, it's in A.
Just put your big boy pants on.
This is rock and roll.
Let's go, guys.
Ready?
Come on, baby.
♪ Fee fi foe fum ♪
♪ I smell the blood ♪
♪ We gotta go now, honey ♪
♪ Big man is coming ♪
♪ Ain't gonna find me ♪
♪ We gotta run ♪
♪ Here comes the edge now ♪
♪ It's time to jump ♪
♪ It always happens
the same way ♪
♪ There's always one more
price to pay ♪
♪ And nothing ventured
Nothing gained ♪
♪ But in the end
It's all the same ♪
♪ Terminal velocity ♪
♪ It only hurts
when you breathe ♪
♪ Tell me you can roll
that ball so fast ♪
♪ I don't know how much longer ♪
♪ I can last ♪
♪ Hi ho silver ♪
♪ Gettin' ready to go ♪
♪ Two desperados run to Mexico ♪
♪ Sham some men tell me ♪
♪ Nowhere left to go ♪
♪ I got a bullet for me ♪
♪ I got a bullet for you ♪
♪ It always happens
the same way ♪
♪ Only the lies have changed ♪
♪ Another life that
we've both lived ♪
What's she doing?
What she's supposed to.
♪ But in the end it's
always the same ♪
♪ Terminal velocity ♪
♪ It only hurts
when you breathe ♪
♪ They tell me you can
only fight so fast ♪
♪ I don't know how much
longer I can last ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Oh man, they're waiting in line!
Yeah.
Since when do you smoke?
Since when do
you care what I do?
Hey.
You about ready?
Yeah,
she's fine, she's just drunk.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, okay.
Whoa, whoa.
Back up, back up,
give her some air.
Hey, you all right?
You okay?
Did you take something?
I don't know.
How did I do that?
Come on, all right.
Come on,
come on, come on.
All right,
nothing to see here. Come on.
Let's go.
Dude,
turn that fucking thing off!
Now that I
knew she could deliver,
I had to get Rick on board.
He'd been avoiding me
after our last fuck up,
but I knew the bartender
at his favorite restaurant.
- Ricky!
- Oh, you got to be kidding me.
You don't write,
you don't call?
We got nothing
to talk about, okay?
I gave you a shot, right?
- You blew it.
- No, look at this, look at this.
Struck by lightning.
Dead for three hours.
Her mom killed
right next to her.
It's a rock and roll tragedy.
I saw the whole thing.
She died?
Yeah, and then she
came back to life
for our sins.
That's quite a lot for you.
Congratulations.
For me?
This guy,
- we had some times.
- Oh, yeah?
- Crazy times, yeah.
- All right, let me talk to you.
- Yeah, what's your name?
- Tracey.
Oh, hey, hey, hey,
Jimmy, nice to meet you.
- Have we met before?
- No.
- No?
- What do you need?
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Vegas or something?
No, why are you
doing this to me?
Just give it a listen, please.
Why?
Come on,
we got a bunch of new songs.
There's a clip
from her performance.
Why?
She's possessed, it's crazy.
I'm telling you.
You want me to get on
my knees or something?
Yeah, I do.
I've been on my knees
since I got into this business.
Come on, just give it a listen.
All right.
I'll do that.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Take it easy, man.
Stop doing this, okay?
You're all frantic.
- All right.
- You seem crazy.
Thanks, Rick.
Tracey, pleasure.
Whoa.
Okay.
Hey, what you doing?
Daddy duty.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, I remember when
Chloe was that young,
that little soft
spot on her head.
You ever think you'd
have a 20-year-old?
I never thought
I'd live to be 20.
So, I know you're all cozy
there and everything, but...
we need you over here.
Right now?
Yeah, uh, Rachel's coming over.
I need to redo the guitar parts,
we need harmonies.
So, get your ass over here.
Jimmy, dude, it's late.
Yeah, you know what, I get it.
It's cool.
I'll just call my buddy,
Owen, up.
He's an amazing guitar player.
He could probably sing
some harmonies, too.
Okay, all right.
That's my boy.
See you soon.
Take her?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's all right.
Baby, you seen my keys?
Uh, yeah, here.
Where are you going?
Jimmy's.
You didn't say this...
was an every-night thing.
It's not.
I miss you.
After a long day
of taking care of her,
I need someone
to take care of me, too.
I miss us.
I mean, you're either sleeping
or you're with her.
She'll sleep through
the night soon.
Carrie...
We haven't had sex in months.
Is that why you stay
over there until 4:00 a.m.?
No.
Jimmy likes to work late.
Jimmy, and...?
Rachel.
And you're with her
and some pervy old guy.
Pervy?
Carrie, come on.
I looked him up.
Okay, so he's someone
you can look up.
Maybe that's all
you need to know.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Look, it's just...
This is a once
in a lifetime thing for me.
This...
this right here...
is a once in a lifetime thing.
...is about to pound this area
with some gusty winds,
torrential rain,
and a lot of lightning,
unfortunately.
And of course,
people who are outside...
I could've stopped it,
but I didn't.
She made him better.
When she changed,
we all changed.
She was a force of nature.
Hell, she even
started booking gigs.
She got us a wedding
that paid ten grand
for one night.
I'm not too proud.
What's gotten into her?
Girl's got the devil in her.
And a liter of vodka.
It's like she's
a completely different person.
She'll say something,
and then you'll remind
her about it the next day
and then she won't
even remember it.
I know what
you're talking about.
I've seen that.
She blacks out.
Listen, she's an artist.
She hears voices.
You're a songwriter.
You know what that's like.
That lightning did something
to her, I'm telling you.
Can't have rock and roll
without electricity.
We're all electricity
when you think about it.
Every thought we have,
synapsis...
She needs help.
Listen, those voices in her head
are our ticket to ride.
Bitch better have my money!
Rachel, you all right?
Jesus Christ.
Here you go, daddy.
Cash money.
Yeah, I think the bride's dad
was in the Armenian mafia
or something.
We haven't even talked
about the fact that, um...
a guy died
in the parking lot tonight.
I don't remember any of that.
You don't remember
an ambulance and a dead guy?
He was, like, they said
27, heart attack, right?
Did you say heart attack?
Heart attack?
Yeah, right.
Later we found out the LAPD
didn't know what to call it.
They had no idea what
they were dealing with.
Neither did we.
Well, I heard at
the Animal Benefit
that this guy, well,
he also died of a heart attack.
She's breaking hearts already.
I'm tired.
Yeah.
You should be,
that was a hell of a show.
You just need
to calm down a little.
No, I need to speed up
and catch up on all
the stuff that I missed out on.
No, you need to relax.
Okay.
Help me.
I can't.
I need you to.
Jesus.
Rachel...
What, are you my mother?
Between your judging
and your pushing me
all the time,
it's like she never left.
Don't you think
you've had enough?
Fuck you, Jimmy.
I mean, who are you
to be lecturing anybody
about anything?
I mean, after all, Jimmy,
you're just a one-hit wonder,
a two-time felon,
three-time divorcée,
no talent ex-junkie.
Well, you figured me out.
Now just...
why don't you get
the fuck out of here?
Everybody just calm down
for a second.
And what about that
record deal, Grandpa?
Record deal you pissed away?
The record deal I don't need
any of you for?
Okay, you know what?
You fucking two
deserve each other.
I'm out of here.
Poor baby.
What about you, Jimmy?
You want a taste?
Does this look tempting at all?
Come on.
No thanks, I'm allergic.
Whenever I do it,
I break out in handcuffs.
Come on, suck it.
You know what?
Let's get you home.
You want to take me home?
What's wrong with you?
You know...
we all carry the seeds of
our own destruction, Mr. Klein.
Wow, this is too fun.
So there I am,
scared out of my sack,
throat burning like hell,
mind fucking blown.
Was the coke laced?
Was I hallucinating?
I didn't know what the fuck.
The only thing I knew for sure
was that wasn't Rachel anymore.
Weeks went by,
she disappeared again.
I was dealing with my own
personal freak out,
and the boys were left wondering
what the hell happened?
Fuck, it's been two weeks.
What do we do?
We got to start jamming again.
Yeah, well,
it looks like it's just going
to be you and me.
I don't know.
She won't call me back and...
I guess it's over.
What's over, your new
relationship or the band?
Fuck you, dude, okay, shut up.
Why would we put
this much energy into it
just to watch it crumble?
This makes no fucking sense.
Do we even need her?
Yeah, we need her.
And you have to admit,
man, there's...
What does Jimmy say
we should do?
I don't know, I mean...
It's undeniable,
she's one of a kind, dude.
She's...
She has something
really special that
a lot of people want
that you can't learn.
Yeah.
Scott was crushed.
It was like a break up to him.
But heartache's good
for a songwriter,
not so good for a marriage.
♪ Blue sky ♪
♪ Blue sky goodbye ♪
You woke her up.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
What are you even doing?
It's, like,
four o'clock in the morning.
I just lost track of time,
I'm sorry.
What is...
What is this?
It's just something
I'm working on, I'm...
"Blue Sky Goodbye."
Is this about her?
No, no, is it...
Is this fucking about her?
You said it was over.
It is over, it's over.
Well, but...
What, you're still, what?
Pining away for her?
- Are you serious?
- Let's not...
You're still fucking
pining away for...
No, come on, baby.
- No, no.
- Stop it, stop it.
Don't touch me,
- don't touch me!
- Stop, stop, stop!
Don't fucking touch me!
Just get out!
Just get the fuck out.
I'm sorry!
Fuck!
President Clinton tries to avoid
a government shutdown.
In entertainment news today,
James Klein,
aka, singer Jimmy Kleen,
was stabbed today
at Los Angeles County Jail
while awaiting arraignment
on a parole violation.
Doctors at City Hospital
say Mr. Klein
is lucky to be alive,
but will never sing again.
And the weather forecast,
overnight lows tonight at...
Look at you!
Look at you,
thanks for calling.
Yeah, man,
thanks for coming over.
Looking good.
I feel good.
Better than ever.
I want you to hear something.
Wow, have you been
digging through the archives?
I recorded that last night.
What? I thought you
couldn't sing though. How?
It's a long story.
How are you?
Good, how's it going?
- Hi.
- Good.
Thanks for coming.
Yeah.
Uh, I listened.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I love it.
Thanks.
She seemed like the old Rachel,
but I couldn't be sure.
No pictures, please.
Jimmy,
so what is fame?
What is fame?
All right.
See this?
To me, it's just
a 25-cent piece of plastic.
To them,
it's a family fucking heirloom.
Fifty-three-year-old bad boy,
what a joke.
I'm going to say
you don't look a day over 52.
What? You motherfucker.
What?
Let me have one of those.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Dude, you just
got your voice back.
You shouldn't be smoking.
Whatever happened to my voice
had nothing to do with this.
What did happen?
What?
She just kissed it
and made it better.
All right, very funny.
Fine, if you don't want to
talk about it, it's fine.
No, she just kissed my neck.
I got some crazy shock,
and then...
hurt like a motherfucker.
So, what, she...
she kissed you and cured you?
You know what, I said
she had mental problems,
not magical powers.
I've had every test
known to man,
but doctors don't know
what the fuck happened.
He wants to write me up
in a medical journal.
Yeah, at least somebody
wants to write about you again.
Getting high and rock and roll
go together like tits and ass,
but now she was just
killing for fun.
Coming in hot!
It's ten in the morning.
Ooh, so?
Yeah, so?
I like your ride, Jimmy.
Thanks.
Is everything sparkling to you?
What are you high on?
I'm high on life, Jimmy!
Of course, I had no idea.
But goddamn it,
every time she took another hit,
we made another hit.
It's got to be worth something,
right?
♪ I feel you
in the autumn breeze ♪
♪ And I smell you
in the gentle fallen leaves ♪
♪ And I see you
every single day ♪
♪ When all I want is
for you to just go away ♪
♪ Fade away from me ♪
♪ Mm-hm ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Fade away from me ♪
♪ Mm, fade away ♪
Right after that,
Rick's girlfriend made him
listen to the demo.
And we got that
record deal after all.
We were signed,
but we had to get Rick
to support the record.
I knew what he wanted for that.
So I threw a party
to set the mood.
Hi, guys, it's your girl Kami,
and you are hashtag blessed
for pressing play
because we are here
at the Hollow Body
record release party
with bad boy Jimmy Kleen.
Jimmy, thanks for joining us.
Yeah, it's my pleasure.
Yes, and you're back!
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Back from the dead.
Clean living.
Stay in school, don't do drugs.
Oh, and there's the lead singer,
Rachel.
Who's that she's with?
- Who knows?
- Whoa!
- She's a wild child.
- Huh.
Just give me a second,
all right?
Uh, pardon me.
Sorry, bud, can you just
back off, all right bud?
She's grinding on me, asshole.
All right, calm down,
calm down.
- Sorry, excuse me.
- Okay, no worries.
Dude, turn that off.
- Come on.
- Dude, he hit me!
Hey, hey,
what the fuck, Jimmy?
Rick's going to be here
any minute.
Can you stay sober
for five fucking minutes?
You had your fun,
I'm having mine.
Listen, you said
you wanted a record deal.
Well, here it is,
so don't fucking blow it.
I said I wanted
to be in a band.
Well, you are in a band.
Now it's time to hit
the high notes.
We're not even
performing tonight.
Well, Rick's not sure
about distribution, all right?
So if you can just put on
a little private performance
for him.
Convince him.
Let's not mince words.
I fuck him,
he pushes the record?
Rock and roll.
Hey. Hey, what the hell
was that? You all right?
I'm fine.
What's gotten into you?
Isn't this what you wanted?
I wanted you to be
a better performer.
I like the old you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, are you okay?
Okay, all right,
come on, outside somewhere.
...parking, get her outside,
sort her out.
All right.
Wait for him there.
Don't say anything stupid.
Oh, hi, you're, um,
- you're Rick Rollins and I'm...
- Yeah.
I'm a such
a fan of your label.
I play drums in Hollow Body.
- Rick. Hey.
- This is Jimmy.
- Thank you for coming, bro.
- Good to see you.
- You met Zach, the drummer.
- I did.
You okay?
No.
You're bad.
You are.
Please.
I'm not dead.
Aren't you?
Rachel, this is Rick.
Hey, I'd shake hands,
but I'll give you this instead.
Save me from this scene.
All right.
Where are they going?
Don't worry about it,
all right? Settle down.
I got to be honest with you.
I know you're
an artist and everything,
but you're so fucking hot.
The only thing on my mind is,
excuse me, fucking.
You know,
I got a place down in Cabo,
we should go down there.
We could do some songwriting,
we can get to know
each other better.
I got a plane out at
the Santa Monica airport,
we can get down there
in about two hours.
All right, Rick.
And just in case you
don't make me come,
let's talk business.
I'm sorry?
I want to open
for your biggest act.
I want a publishing deal,
I keep 50 percent
of whatever the band makes,
and I want a million
in marketing.
To start.
Wow.
May I ask you
a personal question?
Anything.
How old are you?
Because you seem
very mature for your age.
I'm older than I look.
Well, you got fabulous genes.
I get them from
my mother's side.
Why don't we move somewhere
a little bit more...
private?
I'd love to.
Zach,
he loves playing the drums.
- Where are you going?
- Just move.
Whoa, whoa, or what?
What are you gonna
head-butt me too?
I might just throw
you in the fucking pool.
- Stop it.
- Oh, you're drunk.
All right, we'll get you home.
Yeah, where's home, huh?
What, the house
that Carrie kicked me out of
or the apartment I can't afford?
What's your fucking
wife's problem?
You didn't even touch her.
The problem is I wanted to.
But you decided not to
do anything, all right?
And that was a choice.
Yeah.
So deal with it.
Is that her choice?
No one's holding
a gun to her head.
Hang on a second.
Something's not right.
You just need to relax.
Yeah?
Let it happen.
It's done.
Let's go have a cigarette.
I think I've earned it.
I can see why she likes you.
Rachel?
Rachel.
♪ Oh, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ You're dead like me ♪
♪ Hey, you're dead like me ♪
Get out.
Get out!
Rachel.
Wake up, wake up.
Rachel?
Rachel.
She's gone.
Yeah.
Rachel.
Scott didn't know
what hit him.
When he woke up,
all he remembered was
that he finally got
what he wanted,
and regretted it.
You'd think that killing
the head of your label
would be a bad thing.
Out of respect for the family,
I told Rick's dad
it was a heart attack.
They've been
going around lately.
So next thing you know,
he's talking about
throwing a benefit concert,
and guess who managed
to get on the line up?
Please come.
How can we afford it?
You're not getting paid.
Well, it's a benefit.
I mean, nobody's getting paid.
An infant does not belong
at a rock concert.
We'll get, like,
little baby headphones
or something.
Please, this is, like,
the biggest show
I've ever played.
Good for you.
You got everything you wanted.
No, not everything.
I...
Oh, Carrie.
- No, I...
- Come on, don't.
Carrie.
Richie was a great friend,
a brother, really.
Struck down in his prime.
Yeah, well,
that's why we're here, right?
Make something good
come out of it.
Can we just, um,
talk about the heart attacks?
'Cause every gig we do,
someone dies.
What, are we cursed?
This is a benefit
for heart disease.
Have a fucking heart.
We're just gonna sit here
and act like
nothing's happening?
Just stick to the music,
- please, man!
- Dude!
People die all the time.
Okay, well, let's just keep
doing the interview.
Talk about the first night,
the party.
Well, technically,
we crashed that party.
Technically? Definitely.
Thank God you did.
I got something for you.
Yeah?
Earned it.
No, dude.
Yeah.
- You serious?
- Serious.
Hi, babies.
Wow.
You like?
You know it's raining out there.
You're gonna be freezing.
Don't worry about me, baby.
I'll outlive all of you.
What are we drinking to?
Hmm, me.
How you feeling?
Never better.
You'll never guess who's here.
Surprise.
Carrie?
- You're...
- Hey.
You look great.
- How's she doing?
- Great.
- Nice headphones.
- I thought you'd like them.
- What are you doing here?
- It wasn't me, it was...
it was Rachel.
She arranged for us to come
and wanted to surprise you.
- Thanks.
- Are you all right?
Yeah, no, I'm much better now.
Hollow Body, you're next.
About time.
Come, let's go freshen up
in my dressing room real quick.
Rachel, we don't
have time for that.
Relax, can't start without me.
We did it, man,
just like I promised you.
Yeah.
Come on, man,
I thought you'd be happier.
You've dreamt about this
since the moment I met you.
Yeah,
but just not like this, man.
Yeah, well, it's never
the way you want it to be.
Dude, you're just...
you're not hearing me though.
- It's...
- You're right, I'm not.
Jimmy...
Wow. This is, uh...
this is pretty amazing.
Don't think I've ever...
been in a room
with this many mirrors before.
Yeah, it's kind of, um...
a pre-show ritual.
You get what you need?
Oh, yeah.
All right, boys.
Where's Carrie?
She'll be down in a minute.
Don't worry, she's got
the best seat in the house.
Could you take a picture
of me before the show?
Yeah.
I fucking knew it.
Oops.
Yeah, about that...
You know, Carrie,
you're very sweet.
But Scott doesn't want sweet.
He wants me.
They're waiting for us, Rachel.
Yeah, but you're not Rachel,
are you?
Not since the accident.
Those heart attacks,
that you, too?
Who do you think you are?
Look at me.
You don't know what Scott wants.
You think I'm sweet?
There's more to me.
Yeah?
You don't know me.
You don't know my family.
You don't know Scott.
What do you...
You fucking...
Mm.
Oh!
Oh.
You're bad.
It's show time.
People, it's time, you're on!
Jimmy, dude, what the hell
are we gonna do?
We play.
With that?
Oh, I've played with worse.
Dude, we're gonna...
- Jimmy.
- Come on. Let's go!
This is unbelievable.
Zach, dude...
Ladies and gentlemen,
from Hollywood, California,
Hollow Body.
The strike killed us instantly.
The fire took another
nine people.
Injured? I don't know, 50.
But you know what?
They never found Rachel.
Not a trace.
Vanished.
Always leave them wanting more.
They say death
is the ultimate career move.
I should know.
What can I say?
It's a living.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, fade away ♪
♪ Fade away ♪
♪ Mm, fade away, fade away ♪
♪ Fade away, fade away ♪
♪ Fade away
Fade away, fade away ♪
♪ Fade away, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, oh ♪
♪ Won't you
Won't you, won't you fade ♪
♪ Oh, don't you fade away ♪
♪ Fade away, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I wanna know ♪
♪ What I think about you ♪
♪ Well, I don't know yet ♪
♪ What I think about myself ♪
♪ All I know
is when I'm around you ♪
♪ My cares just fade away ♪
♪ What can I say? ♪
♪ I love you in every way ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
♪ So, now I know ♪
♪ How I feel about you ♪
♪ But I cannot tell you ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't wanna
scare you away ♪
♪ How can I tell you
that I think about you ♪
♪ Every night and day ♪
♪ What can I say? ♪
♪ I love you in every way ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
♪ You make the world
worth fighting for ♪
♪ With all their hate
and all their wars ♪
♪ With all their hate and wars ♪
♪ They're always
knocking on my door ♪
♪ Now I know what it's all for ♪
♪ You make the world
worth fighting for ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
♪ You make the world
worth fighting for ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
♪ You make the world
worth fighting for ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
♪ It's just so perfect ♪
♪ You make the world
worth fighting for ♪
♪ It's just a perfect day ♪
Mom?
Dead like me.
Subtitles by explosiveskull